A Guide to the Margaret Freeman Cabell Papers 1910-1982
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series I--Personal Correspondence, n.d. 1866-1978
  - Mally, E. Louise 1936 (Box 9)
  - Manahan, Anastasia and John E. 1971 (Box 9)
  - Monchester, William R. 1949 (Box 9)
  - Maner, William Lawton, Jr. 1949 (Box 9)
  - Mangione, Jerre 1964 (Box 9)
  - March, Michael 1932 (Box 9)
  - Markey, Morris, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Marks, Wirt P., Jr. (see also Christain, Marks, Scott and Spicer Law Offices) 1958 (Box 10)
  - Marshall, Armina 1958-1976 (Box 10)
  - Martin, Ronald E. 1964 (Box 10)
  - Mason, H. Norton, M.D., n.d. (Box 10)
  - Massie, David Hill 1950 (Box 10)
  - Mauer, William 1970 (Box 10)
  - Maxwell, Perriton, n.d. 1933 (Box 10)
  - Mayfield, John S. 1943 (Box 10)
  - Mayfield, Sara 1963-1967 (Box 10)
  - McAdams, George, n.d. (Box 10)
  - McAdams, Thomas B., n.d. 1955 (Box 10)
  - McCain, John Walker, Jr. n.d. (Box 10)
  - McCardell, Roy L. 1929-1949 (Box 10)
  - McDonald, Kenneth M. 1953 (Box 10)
  - McDowell, Frank P.W. 1955-1961 (Box 10)
  - McGee, William 1925 (Box 10)
  - McNeill, Warren A. 1932-1970 (Box 10)
  - McRaye, Walter 1945 (Box 10)
  - Meacham, Harry, n.d. 1954 (Box 10)
  - Meade, Julian R. 1928-1935 (Box 10)
  - Meech, Sylvia Spencer 1935 (Box 10)
  - Meehan, Elizabeth 1932 (Box 10)
  - Mencken, August 1956-1959 (Box 10)
  - Mencken, H.L., n.d. 1949-1961 (Box 10)
  - Meneses, Rose 1974-1976 (Box 10)
  - Metzdorf, Robert F. 1968-1970 (Box 10)
  - Middleton, Mabel 1955 (Box 10)
  - Milne, Alan Alexander 1927 (Box 10)
  - Mitchell, David M. 1932 (Box 10)
  - Mittell, Fannie and Sherman 1941 (Box 10)
  - Moehlman, Arthur Henry 1951-1952 (Box 10)
  - Moffett, Claudia 1949-1956 (Box 10)
  - Moffett, Langston 1947-1950 (Box 10)
  - Montague, Robert Lantane (portrait) 1969 (Box 10)
  - Montgomery, Clare, n.d. 1933 (Box 10)
  - Moody, W.L., Jr. (Mountain Lake Hotel) 1936 (Box 10)
  - Moor, W. Cabell 1933 (Box 10)
  - Moore, Merrill 1936 (Box 10)
  - Moreley-Mower, Geoffrey 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - Moroso, John A. 1931 (Box 10)
  - Morovsky, Calvert 1955-1956 (Box 10)
  - Morris, Ida 1949 (Box 10)
  - Morrison, Robert F. 1949 (Box 10)
  - Morse, Willard S. 1933 (Box 10)
  - Morton, Mary Elizabeth, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Mukerji, Dhan Gopal, n.d. 1936 (Box 10)
  - Mull, Jan Stearns, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Mullins, Helene 1939 (Box 10)
  - Munson, J. John 1936 (Box 10)
  - Myers, Curtis F. 1938-1955 (Box 10)
  - Myers, Cyril B. 1940 (Box 10)
  - Nathan, George Jean 1925 (Box 10)
  - Neal, Earl, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Neilson, Wallace R. 1949 (Box 10)
  - Newcomb, J.L. (University of Virginia) 1935-1954 (Box 10)
  - Newman, Frances, n.d. 1921-1926 (Box 10)
  - Nichols, Robert, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Nicholson, Meredith 1916-1919 (Box 11)
  - Nightingale, Rufus K. 1966 (Box 11)
  - Nilen, E.A. 1935 (Box 11)
  - Noel, Sterling 1933-1938 (Box 11)
  - Norfleet, Elizabeth 1970-1975 (Box 11)
  - Norman, Charles 1939 (Box 11)
  - North, Sterling (New York World Telegram and Sun) 1953-1955 (Box 11)
  - O'Donnell, Robert J. 1939 (Box 11)
  - O'Shaughnessey, Michael, n.d. (Box 11)
  - O'Sullivan, Vincent, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Oppenheim, James (the Thinker) 1930 (Box 11)
  - Oppenheimer, Eleanor Williams 1976 (Box 11)
  - Orcutt, William Dana 1928 (Box 11)
  - Page, Gerald W. 1967 (Box 11)
  - Page, John B. 1951 (Box 11)
  - Page, Robert S., Jr. 1964 (Box 11)
  - Pape, Frank C. 1950 (Box 11)
  - Parent, Monique (Uiversite de Caen) 1950-1961 (Box 11)
  - Parker, Alvin M. 1977 (Box 11)
  - Parker, Dorothy, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Parker, William (English Journal) 1932 (Box 11)
  - Parks, James, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Parrish, James McCaw, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Payne, L.W., Jr. 1927 (Box 11)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes 1937 (Box 11)
  - Peebles, Anne Dobie 1974 (Box 11)
  - Penzoldt, Fritz 1928 (Box 11)
  - Perkins, Enid Eder 1936 (Box 11)
  - Perndt, L. 1941 (Box 11)
  - Peter, Emmett B., Jr. 1961-1965 (Box 11)
  - Pettee, Edith S. 1932 (Box 11)
  - Pfeiffer, Heinrich (The Artists' Theater) 1940 (Box 11)
  - Pitkin, Walter B. 1929-1931 (Box 11)
  - Pollak, Dr. Valentin 1931-1933 (Box 11)
  - Pollard, Catherine Miller, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Poole, Marion and Abram, n.d. 1974 (Box 11)
  - Pope, Edith, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Porter, Martha Boyd, n.d. 1958 (Box 11)
  - Portwood, Winona Hawthorne 1955-1974 (Box 11)
  - Potter, Nancy A> 1953 (Box 11)
  - Ptter, Ralph 1940 (Box 11)
  - Powell, Louise 1957 (Box 11)
  - Powell, William S. 1942 (Box 11)
  - Pratt, Frank W. 1943-1952 (Box 11)
  - Pratt, H.R. 1932-1954 (Box 11)
  - Pratt, Theodore 1945 (Box 11)
  - Price, Byron (United Nations) 1948 (Box 11)
  - Prokosch, Frederick 1944 (Box 11)
  - Pruette, Lorine 1930-1934 (Box 11)
  - Pyle, Howard 1904 (Box 11)
  - Pyle, Caroline and Howard 1970 (Box 11)
  - Quick, Dorothy 1940-1956 (Box 11)
  - Quinn, Alden H. 1929-1930 (Box 11)
  - Rambo, Lawrence M. 1950 (Box 12)
  - Ramsey, Lenore P. 1945 (Box 12)
  - Randolph, Wassell 1953 (Box 12)
  - Rascoe, Burton 1949 (Box 12)
  - Rascoe, Burton (photocopies) 1918-1922 (Box 12)
  - Rascoe, Burton (photocopies) 1918-1924 (Box 12)
  - Rascoe, Hazel (Mrs. Burton) 1957-1961 (Box 12)
  - Rawlings, Marjorie Kinnan (Mrs. Norton Baskin) 1940-1953 (Box 12)
  - Read, Hernado M. 1947-1957 (Box 12)
  - Ready, Lilian M. 1947 (Box 12)
  - Reamy, Robert N. 1961 (Box 12)
  - Redman, Ben Ray 1921-1936 (Box 12)
  - Reid, Jane Davenport (Commonwealth) 1948 (Box 12)
  - Reilly, Glenn 1932 (Box 12)
  - Reinhard, John R. 1939 (Box 12)
  - Remenyi, Joseph (Nyugat) 1934 (Box 12)
  - Renehan, Jane 1965-1969 (Box 12)
  - Reum, Walter J. 1966 (Box 12)
  - Revell, Frank 1932 (Box 12)
  - Reynolds, Virginia 1947 (Box 12)
  - Riaboff, Mariana 1974 (Box 12)
  - Richard, Arthur Jay 1937 (Box 12)
  - Richardson, Eudora Ramsay 1931-1936 (Box 12)
  - Richardson, Virginia, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Ridgeway, Peter (Art Theatre Club, London) 1930-1931 (Box 12)
  - Rinehart, Mary Roberts 1938 (Box 12)
  - Rischin, Moses 1967 (Box 12)
  - Ritchie, Albert C. 1935 (Box 12)
  - Rittenhouse, Jessie B., n.d. (Box 12)
  - Ritter, Larry Jerome (Richmond News Leader) 1954 (Box 12)
  - Rixson, E. 1934 (Box 12)
  - Robb, Ethel 1966 (Box 12)
  - Roberts, Marguerite 1956 (Box 12)
  - Robinson, James Harvey 1923-1924 (Box 12)
  - Robinson, Wirt 1964 (Box 12)
  - Roe, Rosanna Elizabeth 1921-1925 (Box 13)
  - Rogers, Russell Chapin, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Roosevelt, Polly, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Rosenberger, Francis Coleman 1947-1953 (Box 13)
  - Ross, Arthur Leonard 1935 (Box 13)
  - Rothman, Julius L. 1946-1967 (Box 13)
  - Rottensteiner, Franz 1971 (Box 13)
  - Rouse, H. Blair 1950-1959 (Box 13)
  - Rubin, Louis 1959-1965 (Box 13)
  - Russ, Elmo 1934-1939 (Box 13)
  - Russel, Walter (Mark Twain Memorial) 1935 (Box 13)
  - Rutherford, Tom 1961-1973 (Box 13)
  - Salemsin, Harold J. 1930 (Box 13)
  - Salisbury, William 1929 (Box 13)
  - Saltus, Edgar, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Sampson, C.C. 1934 (Box 13)
  - Sampson, Emma Speed 1934 (Box 13)
  - Samuels, Samuel H. 1928 (Box 13)
  - Scarborough, Dorothy 1928 (Box 13)
  - Schein, Donald E. 1952 (Box 13)
  - Schifrfauer, Herman 1921 (Box 13)
  - Schiffman, Harold 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - Schlegel, Dorothy B. 1957-1961 (Box 13)
  - Schnack, Elizabeth 1959 (Box 13)
  - Schroetter, Hilda Noel 1944-1971 (Box 13)
  - Schuman, Frederick L. 1952 (Box 13)
  - Schwab, Arnold T. 1968 (Box 13)
  - Schwartz, Israel 1934 (Box 13)
  - Scott, Hildreth, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Scott, Mary Wingfield, n.d. 1969-1971 (Box 13)
  - Scott, Mary Wingfield 1980 (Box 13)
  - Scoville, Dorothy (News Journal), n.d. (Box 13)
  - Scura, Dorothy 1971 (Box 13)
  - Seibel, George 1936 (Box 13)
  - Selby, John 1943 (Box 13)
  - Self, Margaret Cabell 1936-1955 (Box 13)
  - Sellman, William M., n.d. 1946 (Box 13)
  - Seydell, Mildred 1942 (Box 13)
  - Shafer, Robert 1959 (Box 13)
  - Shanks, Louise J., n.d. (Box 14)
  - Shaw, Roger, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Shaw, William 1940 (Box 14)
  - Shawn, Ted 1929-1946 (Box 14)
  - Shepherd, Anna D. 1963 (Box 14)
  - Shepherd, Emmet 1946 (Box 14)
  - Sheppard, Walter L., Jr. 1957 (Box 14)
  - Silvette, David, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Sinn, Ephraim Edward 1951 (Box 14)
  - Sklar, Robert 1966 (Box 14)
  - Slanizer, Richard Butler, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Smith, Lewis Worthington (Iowa Author's Club) 1925-1935 (Box 14)
  - Smith, Robert Aura 1958-1959 (Box 14)
  - Smith, Warren Allen 1954-1956 (Box 14)
  - Solente, Germaine, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Southworth, Nancy (Mrs. W.F.) 1964 (Box 14)
  - Spear, Helen 1963 (Box 14)
  - Speare, M. Edward 1950 (Box 14)
  - Spotswood, Claire Myers 1932-1935 (Box 14)
  - Spring, Powell 1943 (Box 14)
  - Stagg, Hunter, n.d. 1933-1950 (Box 14)
  - Stagg, Hunter, n.d. 1946-1952 (Box 14)
  - Stagg, Hunter, n.d. 1946-1952 (Box 14)
  - Stagg, Hunter 1921 (Box 14)
    Letter to Stagg from JBC on Rockbridge Alum Springs
  - Stait, Virginia 1938 (Box 14)
  - Starrett, Vincent 1921-1959 (Box 14)
  - Stavely, Margaret, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Steffe, Edwin 1961 (Box 14)
  - Stellwagen, J.H. 1952-1953 (Box 14)
  - Stevens, Elizabeth 1974 (Box 14)
  - Stevenson, Samuel W. (University of Richmond) 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - Stewart, Florence B. 1932 (Box 14)
  - Steward, Sam M., n.d. (Box 14)
  - Steward, Donald Ogden, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Stokes, Elsie Warren, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Stoll, E., n.d. (Box 14)
  - Stone, Isobel 1932 (Box 14)
  - Street, F.G., Jr. 1934 (Box 14)
  - Street, Mary Dallas, n.d. 1935-1946 (Box 14)
  - Strickland, Judson (Emory Phoneix) 1934 (Box 14)
  - Strode, Hudson 1934-1955 (Box 14)
  - Strunz, Jurgen 1971 (Box 14)
  - Stuart, Elsie (Mrs. Walter Preston), n.d. (Box 14)
  - Suber, Peter Dain 1970 (Box 14)
  - Sullivan, Frank C. 1938 (Box 14)
  - Clairmonte, (Mrs.) Glenn 1947 (Box 14)
  - Swan, Bradford F. (Providence Journal) 1946 (Box 14)
  - Swem, E.G. 1961-1962 (Box 14)
  - Swigart, Eugene, n.d. 1951 (Box 14)
  - Tarrant, Desmond 1958-1970 (Box 14)
  - Tate, Allen (Poetry: A Magazine of Verse) 1932 (Box 14)
  - Taylor, Harvey 1933 (Box 14)
  - Taylor, Walter F. 1956 (Box 14)
  - Thayer, Tiffany 1933 (Box 14)
  - Thesing, Curt 1928 (Box 14)
  - Thomas, Anna O. 1943-1944 (Box 14)
  - Thomas, Lowell 1933 (Box 14)
  - Thomas, Meriwether Graves 1954 (Box 15)
  - Thompson, Basil 1915-1920 (Box 15)
  - Thompson, Edward 1942-1948 (Box 15)
  - Thompson, Morton, n.d. 1938 (Box 15)
  - Thomson, Virgil 1971-1976 (Box 15)
  - Tilden, Henry W. 1936 (Box 15)
  - Tilghman, J. Donnell 1961-1976 (Box 15)
  - Tinker, Edward Larocque 1934 (Box 15)
  - Titus, Horace 1956 (Box 15)
  - Tofte, Arthur R. 1933 (Box 15)
  - Toler, Edward Harrison 1953 (Box 15)
  - Tomlin, Marie 1957-1959 (Box 15)
  - Tompkins, Nellie 1940 (Box 15)
  - Toohey, John Peter 1930 (Box 15)
  - Torrence, Clayton, n.d. 1940-1942 (Box 15)
  - Traylor, Lawrence H. 1968 (Box 15)
  - Tresidder, Argus 1940 (Box 15)
  - Trigg, Emma Gray, n.d. 1938-1975 (Box 15)
  - Troubetzkoy, Amelie Rives 1916-1922 (Box 15)
  - Troubetzkoy, Amelie Rives 1916-1922 (Box 15)
  - Troubetzkoy, Ulrich 1957 (Box 15)
  - Truelove, Fred C., n.d. (Box 15)
  - Tucker, Dr. Beverly R. 1937 (Box 15)
  - Turnbull, Andrew 1957-1961 (Box 15)
  - Turner, Arlin 1962 (Box 15)
  - Turpin, Edna 1937-1952 (Box 15)
  - Tutwiler, Rebe Glasgow 1953 (Box 15)
  - Ulmann, Doris (Box 15)
  - Umansky, Harlan 1932-1953 (Box 15)
  - Unidentified, include postcards from Europe to JBC s (Box 15)
  - Untermeyer, Jean Starr 1921-1939 (Box 15)
  - Untermeyer, Louis 1920-1970 (Box 15)
  - Uzzell, Thomas H. 1936 (Box 15)
  - Van Auken, Sheldon 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Van Deventer, A. 1950 (Box 15)
  - Van Doren, Carl 1929-1959 (Box 15)
  - Van Nortwick, Virginia (Greenwood Theatre) 1938 (Box 15)
  - Van Patten, Nathan 1949 (Box 15)
  - Van Vechten, Carl n.d. (Box 15)
  - Vehrenkamp, Otto H. 1958-1959 (Box 15)
  - Viener, Jacob M. 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Viereck, George Sylvester 1920-1954 (Box 15)
  - Vogel, Ezra 1947 (Box 15)
  - Von Jost, Alexander, n.d. 1926 (Box 15)
  - Wagenknecht, Edward 1945-1946, 1954-1972, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Walbridge, Ethel, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Walbridge, Ethel, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Waldman, Leo H. 1932-1940 (Box 16)
  - Wallis, Rev. Charles L. 1947-1965 (Box 16)
  - Wallace, Lewis 1937 (Box 16)
  - Ward, Harold 1919-1922 (Box 16)
  - Warfel, Harry R. 1949 (Box 16)
  - Warner, Slyvia Townsend 1959 (Box 16)
  - Wates, Cyril G. 1943 (Box 16)
  - Watson, H.F. 1945 (Box 16)
  - Wanchope, George A. 1941 (Box 16)
  - Webb, Clinton, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Weddell, Alexander Wilbourne 1933-1943 (Box 16)
  - Weeks, Janice Farrar 1953 (Box 16)
  - Weil, Frederick Peter, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Weinstein 1946 (Box 16)
  - Wells, Arvin, R. 1962 (Box 16)
  - Wells, J.R., n.d. (Box 16)
  - Wells, William H. 1923 (Box 16)
  - Werbeyer, Herbert 1964-1966 (Box 16)
  - West, Herman Hyatt 1934 (Box 16)
  - Wetherbee, Winthrop, Jr. 1936 (Box 16)
  - Wharton, Carly 1939 (Box 16)
  - Wharton, James 1935 (Box 16)
  - Wheeler, (Mr. and Mrs.) Post 1948 (Box 16)
  - Wheeler-Bennett, John W., n.d. (Box 16)
  - White, Walter 1936 (Box 16)
  - Whitty, J.H. 1927 (Box 16)
  - Wight, Frederick S. 1933 (Box 16)
  - Williams, Berkeley 1975 (Box 16)
  - Williams, Blance Colton 1930 (Box 16)
  - Williams, Ellen 1974-1975 (Box 16)
  - Williams, George 1937 (Box 16)
  - Williams, Jessie Bowling 1948 (Box 16)
  - Williams, J. Scott 1922 (Box 16)
  - Williams, Stanley 1930 (Box 16)
  - Willison, J. Russell 1961 (Box 16)
  - Wilson, Douglas 1946 (Box 16)
  - Wilson, Edmund 1955-1974 (Box 16)
  - Wilson, Franklin T., n.d. 1956-1957 (Box 16)
  - Wilson, James Southall (University of Virginia) 1932-1948 (Box 16)
  - Wilson, Julia (Mrs. James Southall), n.d. (Box 16)
  - Winn, Mary Day 1965 (Box 16)
  - Wise, Ellen Wright 1971 (Box 16)
  - Wise, Henry A. 1957 (Box 16)
  - Witt, Ellen Caskie 1957 (Box 16)
  - Witticher, Kathryn 1963 (Box 16)
  - Wood, A.L.S., n.d. (Box 16)
  - Wood, Clement, n.d. 1927 (Box 16)
  - Wood, Gene 1956 (Box 16)
  - Wood, Ray, n.d. 1938-1940 (Box 16)
  - Wood, Virginia H., n.d. (Box 16)
  - Woodford, Jack 1930-1955 (Box 16)
  - Wooding, Grace (Mrs. John Marshall) 1955 (Box 16)
  - Woodward, Harry, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Wright, John W. 1932-1938 (Box 16)
  - Wycherley, H. Alan 1964-1970 (Box 16)
  - Wynn, William T. 1933-1946 (Box 16)
  - Yeatts, J.M. 1956 (Box 16)
  - Yohalem, George 1960 (Box 16)
  - Yorck, Ruth L. 1958 (Box 16)
  - Young, Stark 1936 (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1920-1980 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Items, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous JBC Correspondence 1939, 1946 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous JBC Correspondence concerning There Were Two Pirates, n.d. not addressed (Box 17)
- Series II--Miscellaneous, n.d. 1950-1975
  - Comedy, Irony, Satire (A Definition) by JBC (Box 18)
  - Bills 1952-1975 (Box 18)
  - Insurance 1950-1975 (Box 18)
  - Jurgen: A TV Musical Script (Box 18)
  - Maps, n.d. (Box 18)
  - Marjorie Kinan Rawlings signature to JBC, n.d. (Box 18)
  - News Clippings (Box 18)
  - News Clippings (Box 18)
  - News Clippings (Box 18)
  - News Clippings (Box 18)
  - Proofs, n.d. (Box 18)
  - Proofs-- Balthazar's Daughter (Box 18)
  - Proofs-- James Branch Cabell: The Man and His Masks (Box 19)
  - Proofs-- Something About Eve (Box 19)
  - Proofs-- Storisende (Box 19)
  - Review of Jurgen (Box 19)
  - Schroetter, Samuel, Jr., n.d. (Box 19)
  - Stocks (Box 19)
- Series III--Personal Materials, n.d. 1948-1953
  - Address Book (Box 19)
  - Awards 1953 (Box 19)
  - Ballard Cabell-Funeral, clipping Virginia Genealogical Society card, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Photographs, n.d. (1980 of 2301 Monument Ave.), misc. negatives (Box 19)
  - Book Covers, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence--JBC and BHC to MWF (envelopes for which there are no letters) 1949-1950 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence-JBC and BHC to MWF 1948-1952 (Box 20)
  - Genealogy (Box 20)
  - Genealogy Correspondence (Box 20)
  - Genealogy-MFC (Box 20)
  - Genealogy--MFC (Box 20)
  - Marriage Certificate 1950 (Box 20)
  - Wedding of J.B. Cabell and M.W. Freeman 1950 (Box 21)
  - Wills (Box 21)
- Series IV--Organizational Correspondence, n.d. 1926-1977
  - Academy of American Poets 1971-1975 (Box 21)
  - Accent(formerly Direction) 1940 (Box 21)
  - ACHSHAV Publishing House Israel ed. of Jurgen 1978 (Box 21)
  - Agenzia Litteraria Internazionale 1973-1975 (Box 21)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Industries 1975 (Box 21)
  - American Bar Association (Lewis F. Powell, Jr.) 1964 (Box 21)
  - American Caravan(Alfred Kreymborg) 1926-1927 (Box 21)
  - American Foundation for Overseas Blind, Inc. (Helen Keller) 1955-1956 (Box 21)
  - American Historical Company, Inc. (Winfield Scott Downs) 1955-1961 (Box 21)
  - American Mercury(Paul Palmer) 1935-1937 (Box 21)
  - American National Red Cross (Jacob M. Viener) 1977 (Box 21)
  - American Spectator 1932-1935 (Box 21)
  - American Writers' Commitee Against Lynching 1933 (Box 21)
  - AMS Press 1969 (Box 21)
  - Anglo-German Literary Agency 1971-1974 (Box 21)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts, Inc. (Helen Cohan) 1956 (Box 21)
  - Argus Book Shop (Ben Abramson) 1933-1944 (Box 21)
  - Aristocrat(Lewis Carter Randolph) 1933 (Box 21)
  - Arizona, State of (M.L. Brooks and Lillian B. Johnston) 1950-1951 (Box 21)
  - Arthritis and Rhematism Foundation 1958 (Box 21)
  - Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities 1958-1974 (Box 21)
  - Atlantic Monthly(Edward Weeks) 1932-1951 (Box 21)
  - Audubon Magazine(John K. Terres) 1955 (Box 21)
  - Aurand's Booksellers and Publishers (A.M. Aurand, Jr.) 1936 (Box 21)
  - Aviles Book Shop and Rental Library (Sally Akin) 1943 (Box 21)
  - Avon Books (Peter Mayer) 1965-1969 (Box 21)
  - Ballantine Books, Inc. 1968-1972 (Box 21)
  - Barrow Restoration Shop, Inc. 1976 (Box 21)
  - Berkshire County Records Office (Peter Walne) 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Black Productions, Inc. 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - Black Mack (Thomas W. MacDonald), n.d. 1941 (Box 22)
  - Blanton's Package Delivery, Inc. 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - Bodley Head, Ltd. (John Lane) 1930-1971 (Box 22)
  - Bond, Nelson 1947-1949 (Box 22)
  - Bond, Nelson 1970-1974 (Box 22)
  - Bookman 1919-1930 (Box 22)
  - Book of the Month Club 1935 (Box 22)
  - Book Parade(Russel Sanjek) 1956 (Box 22)
  - Books for Libraries, Inc. 1967-1970 (Box 22)
  - Botetourt Bibliographical Society 1967, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Botetourt Bibliographical Society 1968
  - Branch and Co. 1960s-1970 (Box 22)
  - Brandt and Brandt Dramatic Department, Inc. (Harold Freedman) 1954-1966 (Box 22)
  - Brooklyn Public Library (George W. Wakefield) 1965 (Box 22)
  - Brown University 1968 (Box 22)
  - Cabell Memorial Foundation 1963-1973 (Box 22)
  - Cabell Memorial Foundation, n.d. 1958-1972 (Box 22)
  - Cabell Society (William Godshalk) 1968-1972 (Box 22)
  - Cabell Society, n.d. 1969-1975 (Box 22)
  - Candlelight Press (Peter A. Ruber) 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Centaur Book Shop (Harold T. Mason) 1933-1938 (Box 22)
  - Chappel. Col., Inc. 1962 (Box 22)
  - Christian, Marks, Scott and Spicer Law Offices 1955-1956 (Box 23)
  - Christian Science Committee on Publication 1965 (Box 23)
  - Cleveland Plain Dealer 1956 (Box 23)
  - Cokesbury 1969, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Collectors' Old Book Shop (Roane), n.d. 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - College of William and Mary (Joshua B. Mitchell) 1955-1968 (Box 23)
  - College and University Press 1970 (Box 23)
  - Colonial Dames of America 1955-1969 (Box 23)
  - Colonial Dames of America 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Colonial Dames of America 1962-1970 (Box 23)
  - Colophon(Elmer Adler) 1936-1938 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Pictures, n.d. (Box 23)
  - Committee of Southern Writers 1932 (Box 23)
  - Confederate Chapel, n.d. 1970, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Confederate Museum, n.d. 1970, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Copyright Office, Library of Congress, n.d. 1948-1963 (Box 23)
  - Cornell University Library 1959 (Box 23)
  - Crowell (Thomas Y.) Company 1960 (Box 23)
  - Crown Publisher, Inc. (Joseph H. Reiner) 1960-1965 (Box 23)
  - Crown Publishers 1961-1975 (Box 23)
  - Cuna Mutual Insurance Company 1957 (Box 23)
  - Dartmouth College Library 1948 (Box 23)
  - Davenport and Co. 1975-1977 (Box 23)
  - Day Company, Inc., Publishers, n.d. 1925 (Box 23)
  - Daye (Stephen) Press 1946 (Box 23)
  - Decorators Club, Inc. 1957 (Box 23)
  - Deal Harvey 1969-1970 (Box 23)
  - Dent (J.M.) and Sons 1963 (Box 23)
  - Detroit Public Library 1969 (Box 23)
  - Dial Press 1928 (Box 23)
  - Dictionary of Literary and Dramatic Criticism 1923-1941 (Box 23)
  - Diogenes Verlag, Daniel Keel 1958 (Box 23)
  - Direction(Kerker Quinn), n.d. (Box 23)
  - Doubleday and Company, Inc. 1961-1965 (Box 23)
  - Doubleday and Co., 1970 (Box 23)
  - Doubleday, Doran and Company 1931-1957 (Box 23)
  - Dover Publications 1976-1978 (Box 23)
  - Dutton (E.P.) and Company, Inc. 1936 (Box 23)
  - Elk Hill Farm, Inc. 1974 (Box 23)
  - Ellen Glasgow Society (Membership Rooster), n.d. (Box 23)
  - Encyclopedia of American Biography 1958-1960 (Box 23)
  - English Speaking Union 1969-1974 (Box 23)
  - Epilepsy Foundation 1963 (Box 24)
  - Essay Annual 1935 (Box 24)
  - Extension Serivce 1953-1959 (Box 24)
  - Farrar and Rinehart, Inc. 1940-1944 (Box 24)
  - Farrar, Straus and Company (John Farrar) 1946-1953 (Box 24)
  - Farrar, Straus and Company (John Farrar, Roger Straus) 1952-1967 (Box 24)
  - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America 1931 (Box 24)
  - Federated Arts of Richmond 1958 (Box 24)
  - Ferguson (J.F.) Publishing Company 1967 (Box 24)
  - First and Merchants National Bank (Clinton Webb) 1959-1975 (Box 24)
  - First and Merchants National Bank 1970-1971 (Box 24)
  - First Families of Virginia 1965-1974 (Box 24)
  - Florida Historical Society 1942-1946 (Box 24)
  - Florida State University 1954 (Box 24)
  - Fortean Society 1937 (Box 24)
  - Fortean Society 1937 (Box 24)
  - Fredricksburg Gallery of Modern Art 1969 (Box 24)
  - Samuel French, Ltd. 1927 (Box 24)
  - Funk and Wagnalls Company 1955 (Box 24)
  - Garden Club of Virginia 1959 (Box 24)
  - Gastonia Gazette 1956 (Box 24)
  - Georgia Review 1953-1954 (Box 24)
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop 1971 (Box 24)
  - Gotham Book Mart and Gallery, Inc. 1970 (Box 24)
  - Governor's Committee for the Handicapped 1961 (Box 24)
  - Greenwood Press, Inc. 1969-1972 (Box 24)
  - Guaranty Trust Company of New York 1955 (Box 24)
  - Hallmark Cards, Inc. 1963-1964 (Box 24)
  - Harbor Press, Inc. 1931 (Box 24)
  - Harcourt, Brace and Company 1959-1961 (Box 24)
  - Harcourt, Brace and Company 1961-1966 (Box 24)
  - Harper and Brothers 1928-1955 (Box 24)
  - Hay (George) 1974 (Box 24)
  - Hereditary Register of the United States of America, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Hill (Laurie) Limited 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation 1957 (Box 24)
  - Historic Richmond Foundation 1957-1975 (Box 24)
  - Holborn Printing and Distributing Company 1958 (Box 24)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc. 1964 (Box 24)
  - International Creative Management (film rights for Silver Stallion) 1972-1975 (Box 24)
  - Jamestowne Society 1959 (Box 24)
  - Jewish Historical Society 1972 (Box 24)
  - Johnson Reprint Corporation 1968-1976 (Box 24)
  - Junior League of Richmond, Virginia 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - Kalki (James N. Hall) 1965-1971 (Box 24)
  - Knopf (Alfred A.), Inc. 1934-1960 (Box 24)
  - Kraus Reprint Company 1969 (Box 24)
  - Lance(Ellington Curtis) 1934-1935 (Box 24)
  - League of American Writers for Wendell L. Wilkie 1940 (Box 1940)
  - Library Reources, Inc. 1970 (Box 24)
  - Life (John CLute) 1962 (Box 24)
  - Limited Editions Club 1974-1977 (Box 24)
  - Lion Bookshop 1958 (Box 24)
  - Lippincott (J.B.) Company 1931-1947 (Box 24)
  - Literary Digest 1933 (Box 24)
  - Literary Guild of America, Inc. 1927 (Box 24)
  - Little, Brown and Company (Box 24)
  - Loews, Theatre 1935 (Box 24)
  - Logress Press 1966 (Box 24)
  - Machen (Arthur) Society 1957-1967 (Box 26)
  - McBride (Robert M.) and Company, n.d. 1927 (Box 26)